<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2024-07-09T23:26:08+12:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/feed.xml</id><subtitle>Hello and welcome to my blog! Here, I document my journey in Landscape Architecture, Graphic Design and IT projects. I am a creative individual who enjoys human-centered design, respecting the relationships between humans, nature, and spaces.</subtitle><author><name>8010</name></author><entry><title type="html">Trademark</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/graphicdesign/2024/07/01/project1/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Trademark" /><published>2024-07-01T00:00:00+12:00</published><updated>2024-07-01T00:00:00+12:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/graphicdesign/2024/07/01/project1</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/graphicdesign/2024/07/01/project1/"><![CDATA[<h2>Purpose of the Project</h2>
<p>Bruce Bay Beans and Bunks, formerly known as the Bruce Bay Coffee Cart, is a small family-owned business situated on the Haast Highway between Haast and Fox Glacier. The business is transitioning from a mobile coffee cart to a permanent building that will also offer simple lodging. Despite the scenic location and quality offerings, the business currently relies on an outdated, in-person only model for handling orders. As it grows, the company aims to better serve its customers, who are primarily tired tourists seeking a convenient way to pre-order coffee and snacks during their journey.</p>]]></content><author><name>8010</name></author><category term="graphicdesign" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Purpose of the Project Bruce Bay Beans and Bunks, formerly known as the Bruce Bay Coffee Cart, is a small family-owned business situated on the Haast Highway between Haast and Fox Glacier. The business is transitioning from a mobile coffee cart to a permanent building that will also offer simple lodging. Despite the scenic location and quality offerings, the business currently relies on an outdated, in-person only model for handling orders. As it grows, the company aims to better serve its customers, who are primarily tired tourists seeking a convenient way to pre-order coffee and snacks during their journey.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Project1</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/more/2024/07/01/project1/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Project1" /><published>2024-07-01T00:00:00+12:00</published><updated>2024-07-01T00:00:00+12:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/more/2024/07/01/project1</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/more/2024/07/01/project1/"><![CDATA[<p>Bruce Bay Beans and Bunks, formerly known as the Bruce Bay Coffee Cart, is a small family-owned business situated on the Haast Highway between Haast and Fox Glacier. The business is transitioning from a mobile coffee cart to a permanent building that will also offer simple lodging. Despite the scenic location and quality offerings, the business currently relies on an outdated, in-person only model for handling orders. As it grows, the company aims to better serve its customers, who are primarily tired tourists seeking a convenient way to pre-order coffee and snacks during their journey.</p>]]></content><author><name>8010</name></author><category term="more" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bruce Bay Beans and Bunks, formerly known as the Bruce Bay Coffee Cart, is a small family-owned business situated on the Haast Highway between Haast and Fox Glacier. The business is transitioning from a mobile coffee cart to a permanent building that will also offer simple lodging. Despite the scenic location and quality offerings, the business currently relies on an outdated, in-person only model for handling orders. As it grows, the company aims to better serve its customers, who are primarily tired tourists seeking a convenient way to pre-order coffee and snacks during their journey.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Motel - Bruce Bay Beans Bunks - Group Project</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/it/2024/06/25/project1/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Motel - Bruce Bay Beans Bunks - Group Project" /><published>2024-06-25T00:00:00+12:00</published><updated>2024-06-25T00:00:00+12:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/it/2024/06/25/project1</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/it/2024/06/25/project1/"><![CDATA[<p>Click to action demo (Pythonanywhere has a time limit, and the links may not work):
    <a href="https://junsunujuss.pythonanywhere.com/">Bruce Bay Beans and Bunks</a>
</p>
<div class="sub-title">Project Overview</div>
<p>Bruce Bay Beans and Bunks, formerly known as the Bruce Bay Coffee Cart, is a small family-owned business situated on the Haast Highway between Haast and Fox Glacier. The business is transitioning from a mobile coffee cart to a permanent building that will also offer simple lodging. Despite the scenic location and quality offerings, the business currently relies on an outdated, in-person only model for handling orders. As it grows, the company aims to better serve its customers, who are primarily tired tourists seeking a convenient way to pre-order coffee and snacks during their journey.
<br /><br />
The business currently faces several challenges. The existing business model restricts Bruce Bay Beans and Bunks' ability to expand and effectively cater to its customers' needs. Without an online system, customers are limited to placing orders in person at the shop, which can be inconvenient. Additionally, manually keeping track of stock levels is challenging and time-consuming, increasing the risk of overstocking or running out of popular items. The shift to offering lodging necessitates the implementation of an online system to manage accommodation bookings.
<br /><br />
To address these issues and facilitate business growth, the project aims to develop a user-friendly online system that allows customers to browse and order food, drinks, and merchandise, and book accommodation effortlessly. This system will streamline the management of orders and bookings, reducing errors and saving time. It will also automate inventory management, enabling real-time tracking of stock levels to ensure popular items are always available while minimising overstock issues. The integration of a secure payment gateway will include GST and support promotion code usage, enhancing customer convenience. Additionally, the system enables various administrative tasks such as account management, promotional activities, and comprehensive reporting, thus reducing the administrative load on staff and improving operational efficiency.
<br /><br />
By addressing these goals, the project aims to solve the current challenges faced by Bruce Bay Beans and Bunks, ensuring a better experience for both customers and staff, and supporting the business's growth and success.</p>]]></content><author><name>8010</name></author><category term="IT" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Click to action demo (Pythonanywhere has a time limit, and the links may not work): Bruce Bay Beans and Bunks Project Overview Bruce Bay Beans and Bunks, formerly known as the Bruce Bay Coffee Cart, is a small family-owned business situated on the Haast Highway between Haast and Fox Glacier. The business is transitioning from a mobile coffee cart to a permanent building that will also offer simple lodging. Despite the scenic location and quality offerings, the business currently relies on an outdated, in-person only model for handling orders. As it grows, the company aims to better serve its customers, who are primarily tired tourists seeking a convenient way to pre-order coffee and snacks during their journey. The business currently faces several challenges. The existing business model restricts Bruce Bay Beans and Bunks' ability to expand and effectively cater to its customers' needs. Without an online system, customers are limited to placing orders in person at the shop, which can be inconvenient. Additionally, manually keeping track of stock levels is challenging and time-consuming, increasing the risk of overstocking or running out of popular items. The shift to offering lodging necessitates the implementation of an online system to manage accommodation bookings. To address these issues and facilitate business growth, the project aims to develop a user-friendly online system that allows customers to browse and order food, drinks, and merchandise, and book accommodation effortlessly. This system will streamline the management of orders and bookings, reducing errors and saving time. It will also automate inventory management, enabling real-time tracking of stock levels to ensure popular items are always available while minimising overstock issues. The integration of a secure payment gateway will include GST and support promotion code usage, enhancing customer convenience. Additionally, the system enables various administrative tasks such as account management, promotional activities, and comprehensive reporting, thus reducing the administrative load on staff and improving operational efficiency. By addressing these goals, the project aims to solve the current challenges faced by Bruce Bay Beans and Bunks, ensuring a better experience for both customers and staff, and supporting the business's growth and success.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Swimming Club - Group Project</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/it/2024/05/25/project2/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Swimming Club - Group Project" /><published>2024-05-25T00:00:00+12:00</published><updated>2024-05-25T00:00:00+12:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/it/2024/05/25/project2</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/it/2024/05/25/project2/"><![CDATA[<p>Click to action demo (Pythonanywhere has a time limit, and the links may not work):
    <a href="http://swimmingclubzz.pythonanywhere.com/">Swimming Club Demo</a>
</p>
<div class="sub-title">Project Overview</div>
<p>The countryside community swimming club situated in a small rural township and run by the local rural community for the local rural community. The club is formed by functional complex featuring with a small of two swimming pools:</p>
<p>- Deep Pool: A various aqua aerobics classes.</p>
<p>- Land Pool: One on one swimming lessons.</p>
<p>The club's activities revolve around aqua aerobics and personalized swimming lessons, and it operates on a membership basis to serve its client.</p>
<div class="sub-title">Project Issue</div>
<p>Currently, the club are facing the challenges with its manual management system, which may lead to inefficiency, errors, management and other problems in the daily management of the club.</p>
<div class="sub-title">Project Aim</div>
<p>In order to streamline the operational efficiency, the club seeks to a develop and a management system that will facilitate a seamless interaction among members, instructors, and club managers. Streamlining the booking processes for aqua aerobics classes and swimming lessons, managing members subscriptions, enable instructors with scheduling capabilities, financial tracking, and allow managers to oversee the club’s activities effectively.</p>
<div class="sub-title">Our issues while working on the project</div>
<p>1.Since we are a small team with only 2 members, we have discussed with the product owner and agreed to focus only on high-priority tasks, according to our team's ability. Additional features will be considered based on time availability. Any related to the instructor and one-on-one lessons will be considered low priority.</p>
<p>2.Lacking a background in IT, resolving bugs has required additional time and effort.</p>
<div class="sub-title">Project Goal</div>
<p>Given the constraints of a small team comprising only two members and the completion of high-priority tasks, the project's overarching goal remains focused on delivering essential functionalities to improve operational efficiency within the Countryside Community Swimming Club. Despite limitations, the project aims to achieve the following objectives:</p>
<p>1.
Core Functionality Implementation:
Prioritize the development and implementation of high priority features essential for streamlining club operations.</p>
<p>2.
Operational Efficiency Enhancement:
Optimize existing manual processes by automating critical functions, including aqua aerobics class bookings and member subscription management, to minimize errors and improve overall efficiency.</p>
<p>3.
User Experience Improvement:
Enhance the user experience by providing members with intuitive interfaces for accessing club services, booking classes, and managing subscriptions, engaging members' satisfaction.</p>
<p>4.
Adaptability and Scalability Consideration:
Design the system with flexibility and scalability in mind to accommodate future growth and expansion.</p>]]></content><author><name>8010</name></author><category term="IT" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Click to action demo (Pythonanywhere has a time limit, and the links may not work): Swimming Club Demo Project Overview The countryside community swimming club situated in a small rural township and run by the local rural community for the local rural community. The club is formed by functional complex featuring with a small of two swimming pools: - Deep Pool: A various aqua aerobics classes. - Land Pool: One on one swimming lessons. The club's activities revolve around aqua aerobics and personalized swimming lessons, and it operates on a membership basis to serve its client. Project Issue Currently, the club are facing the challenges with its manual management system, which may lead to inefficiency, errors, management and other problems in the daily management of the club. Project Aim In order to streamline the operational efficiency, the club seeks to a develop and a management system that will facilitate a seamless interaction among members, instructors, and club managers. Streamlining the booking processes for aqua aerobics classes and swimming lessons, managing members subscriptions, enable instructors with scheduling capabilities, financial tracking, and allow managers to oversee the club’s activities effectively. Our issues while working on the project 1.Since we are a small team with only 2 members, we have discussed with the product owner and agreed to focus only on high-priority tasks, according to our team's ability. Additional features will be considered based on time availability. Any related to the instructor and one-on-one lessons will be considered low priority. 2.Lacking a background in IT, resolving bugs has required additional time and effort. Project Goal Given the constraints of a small team comprising only two members and the completion of high-priority tasks, the project's overarching goal remains focused on delivering essential functionalities to improve operational efficiency within the Countryside Community Swimming Club. Despite limitations, the project aims to achieve the following objectives: 1. Core Functionality Implementation: Prioritize the development and implementation of high priority features essential for streamlining club operations. 2. Operational Efficiency Enhancement: Optimize existing manual processes by automating critical functions, including aqua aerobics class bookings and member subscription management, to minimize errors and improve overall efficiency. 3. User Experience Improvement: Enhance the user experience by providing members with intuitive interfaces for accessing club services, booking classes, and managing subscriptions, engaging members' satisfaction. 4. Adaptability and Scalability Consideration: Design the system with flexibility and scalability in mind to accommodate future growth and expansion.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Wilson Carpark Garden Bed Upgrade</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/landscape/2024/05/24/project1/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Wilson Carpark Garden Bed Upgrade" /><published>2024-05-24T00:00:00+12:00</published><updated>2024-05-24T00:00:00+12:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/landscape/2024/05/24/project1</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/landscape/2024/05/24/project1/"><![CDATA[<div class="cust-p">
  This project aims to maintain the site's amenities and improve a temporary landscape area. The temporary landscape area will be carefully created as a clean and enjoyable space for public.
  <br /><br />
  The primary considerations for selecting plants are "easy maintenance, fast growth, and good drainage."
  <br /><br />
  The project involves landscape design, landscape specifications, and a year of maintenance to ensure the plants are well-established.
</div>]]></content><author><name>8010</name></author><category term="landscape" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[This project aims to maintain the site's amenities and improve a temporary landscape area. The temporary landscape area will be carefully created as a clean and enjoyable space for public. The primary considerations for selecting plants are "easy maintenance, fast growth, and good drainage." The project involves landscape design, landscape specifications, and a year of maintenance to ensure the plants are well-established.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Biosecurity - Individual</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/it/2024/03/25/project3/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Biosecurity - Individual" /><published>2024-03-25T00:00:00+13:00</published><updated>2024-03-25T00:00:00+13:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/it/2024/03/25/project3</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/it/2024/03/25/project3/"><![CDATA[<p>Click to action demo (Pythonanywhere has a time limit, and the links may not work):
    <a href="http://ritachen1126418.pythonanywhere.com/">Biosecurity</a>
    <br />
    Click to
    <a href="https://github.com/Geasssoul/Biosecurity?tab=readme-ov-file">Github</a>
</p>
<div class="sub-title">Project Overview</div>
<p>This project is to develop a Python Web app functioning as a biosecurity guide, providing information on agricultural pests and weeds present in New Zealand. The Web comes with the agricultural theme which is a friendly-use interface that contains three different user roles and access control: Agronomists, Staff and Administrator.</p>
<div class="sub-title">Aim</div>
<p>Understand and learn the permissions of different users.</p>]]></content><author><name>8010</name></author><category term="IT" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Click to action demo (Pythonanywhere has a time limit, and the links may not work): Biosecurity Click to Github Project Overview This project is to develop a Python Web app functioning as a biosecurity guide, providing information on agricultural pests and weeds present in New Zealand. The Web comes with the agricultural theme which is a friendly-use interface that contains three different user roles and access control: Agronomists, Staff and Administrator. Aim Understand and learn the permissions of different users.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">User Experience - Concept Design: Interactive Prototype</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/it/2023/07/25/project4/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="User Experience - Concept Design: Interactive Prototype" /><published>2023-07-25T00:00:00+12:00</published><updated>2023-07-25T00:00:00+12:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/it/2023/07/25/project4</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/it/2023/07/25/project4/"><![CDATA[<p>Lincoln University would like to replace the existing fixed maps with a physical interactive digital map portal. Based on their requriment I have develop a serise Interactive Prototype.</p>
<div class="sub-title">Users</div>
<p>The prototype can be student (international), staff, visitors and disabled also open to the public.</p>
<div class="sub-title">Extra Function to be Added</div>
<p>Able to switch different languages, and an AI function for providing help to disabled.</p>
<div class="sub-title">Interactive Methods</div>
<p>In this prototype, I have considered several interactive methods, e,g: a music player when in low power mode, AI mode, phone call, camera, sensor and a game to engage with different users.</p>]]></content><author><name>8010</name></author><category term="IT" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lincoln University would like to replace the existing fixed maps with a physical interactive digital map portal. Based on their requriment I have develop a serise Interactive Prototype. Users The prototype can be student (international), staff, visitors and disabled also open to the public. Extra Function to be Added Able to switch different languages, and an AI function for providing help to disabled. Interactive Methods In this prototype, I have considered several interactive methods, e,g: a music player when in low power mode, AI mode, phone call, camera, sensor and a game to engage with different users.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Landscape Design - Residential</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/landscape/2023/06/26/project2/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Landscape Design - Residential" /><published>2023-06-26T00:00:00+12:00</published><updated>2023-06-26T00:00:00+12:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/landscape/2023/06/26/project2</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/landscape/2023/06/26/project2/"><![CDATA[<p>This project involves close collaboration with the team to deliver the best outcome in landscape design. My design principle is to create an environment that is both beautiful and practical, while also enhancing privacy between neighbourhoods and offering an exceptional outdoor experience for residents.</p>]]></content><author><name>8010</name></author><category term="landscape" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[This project involves close collaboration with the team to deliver the best outcome in landscape design. My design principle is to create an environment that is both beautiful and practical, while also enhancing privacy between neighbourhoods and offering an exceptional outdoor experience for residents.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Landscape Design - Residential</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/landscape/2023/04/25/project3/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Landscape Design - Residential" /><published>2023-04-25T00:00:00+12:00</published><updated>2023-04-25T00:00:00+12:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/landscape/2023/04/25/project3</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/landscape/2023/04/25/project3/"><![CDATA[<p>This project involves close collaboration with the team to deliver the best outcome in landscape design. My design principle is to create an environment that is both beautiful and practical, while also enhancing privacy between neighbourhoods and offering an exceptional outdoor experience for residents.</p>]]></content><author><name>8010</name></author><category term="landscape" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[This project involves close collaboration with the team to deliver the best outcome in landscape design. My design principle is to create an environment that is both beautiful and practical, while also enhancing privacy between neighbourhoods and offering an exceptional outdoor experience for residents.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Logo</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/graphicdesign/2022/06/25/project2/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Logo" /><published>2022-06-25T00:00:00+12:00</published><updated>2022-06-25T00:00:00+12:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/graphicdesign/2022/06/25/project2</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/graphicdesign/2022/06/25/project2/"><![CDATA[<h2>Abstract</h2>
<p>Bruce Bay Beans and Bunks, formerly known as the Bruce Bay Coffee Cart, is a small family-owned business situated on the Haast Highway between Haast and Fox Glacier. The business is transitioning from a mobile coffee cart to a permanent building that will also offer simple lodging. Despite the scenic location and quality offerings, the business currently relies on an outdated, in-person only model for handling orders. As it grows, the company aims to better serve its customers, who are primarily tired tourists seeking a convenient way to pre-order coffee and snacks during their journey.</p>]]></content><author><name>8010</name></author><category term="graphicdesign" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Abstract Bruce Bay Beans and Bunks, formerly known as the Bruce Bay Coffee Cart, is a small family-owned business situated on the Haast Highway between Haast and Fox Glacier. The business is transitioning from a mobile coffee cart to a permanent building that will also offer simple lodging. Despite the scenic location and quality offerings, the business currently relies on an outdated, in-person only model for handling orders. As it grows, the company aims to better serve its customers, who are primarily tired tourists seeking a convenient way to pre-order coffee and snacks during their journey.]]></summary></entry></feed>